Now, class.
‫والآن، أيها الطلاب.‬
Can anyone tell me what the decision
‫هل يمكن لأحد أن يخبرني علام بُني‬
in the 1968 Stuttgart case was based upon?
‫قرار قضية "شتوتغارت" لعام 1968؟‬
Well? Why is it so quiet?
‫ما الأمر؟ ما هذا الصمت؟‬
Is this a Zen temple in the Orient?
‫أهذا معبد بوذي في بلاد الشرق؟‬
Mr. Eimer. Would you like to venture a guess?
‫سيد "أيمر"، هل تودّ أن تخمّن؟‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
Uh… Well…
‫في الواقع…‬
Well? Can anyone break this silence for us?
‫أيستطيع أحد‬ ‫أن يكسر هذا الصمت المخيّم علينا؟‬
Hmm. I see the habitually tardy one has finally arrived.
‫أرى أن الطالبة التي اعتادت التأخر‬ ‫قد وصلت أخيرًا.‬
You're 13 minutes late.
‫تأخرت 13 دقيقة.‬
It seems that your part-time pizza delivery job was quite busy today.
‫يبدو أن عملك بدوام جزئي‬ ‫في توصيل البيتزا كان حافلًا اليوم.‬
I'm so sorry… Professor Kronecker.
‫أنا آسفة جدًا يا أستاذ "كرونيكر".‬
Before you take your seat, let me ask you a question first.
‫قبل أن تجلسي، دعيني أطرح عليك سؤالًا أولًا.‬
Do you have enough strength to tell me what the basis was
‫ألديك ما يكفي من القوة‬ ‫لتخبريني على أي أساس‬
for the decision in the Stuttgart case?
‫بُني القرار في قضية "شتوتغارت"؟‬
Huh? Oh, yes…
‫ماذا؟‬
The defendant claimed that the kidnapping was a sham
‫زعم المتهم بأن الاختطاف كان تمثيلية‬
and that the victim's death was merely an accident.
‫وأن موت الضحية كان مجرد حادث.‬
After investigating the crime scene,
‫بعد التحقيق في مسرح الجريمة،‬
it was found that the victim's death has indeed been accidental.
‫تبيّن أن موت الضحية كان بسبب حادث فعلًا.‬
It is believed that this is why the defendant was sentenced to 15 years,
‫يُعتقد أن هذا هو السبب‬ ‫في الحكم على المتهم بـ15 عامًا،‬
as intent to kill must be proven in a murder case.
‫لأن نية القتل يجب أن تُثبت في قضية قتل.‬
Very well. Take a seat, Miss Nina Fortner.
‫حسنًا. اجلسي يا آنسة "نينا فورتنر".‬
Thank you, Professor.
‫شكرًا أيها الأستاذ.‬
HEIDELBERG (GERMANY)
‫"(هايدلبرغ)، (ألمانيا)"‬
You saved us, Nina!
‫لقد أنقذتنا يا "نينا"!‬
If no one could give him an answer,
‫لو لم يستطع أحد أن يعطيه جوابًا،‬
Kronecker would probably have wanted us to hand in 50-page reports.
‫لكلّفنا "كرونيكر" على الأرجح‬ ‫بتسليمه مقالات من 50 صفحة.‬
Maybe even 50 pages isn't enough.
‫وقد لا يكتفي حتى بـ50 صفحة.‬
Since we're so indebted to Nina, I have to treat her to something to eat.
‫بما أننا مدينون لـ"نينا"،‬ ‫يجب أن أدعوها إلى شيء تأكله.‬
How about today, Nina? Just the two of us…
‫ما رأيك في اليوم يا "نينا"؟ نحن فقط…‬
NINA FORTNER
‫آسفة يا "بيتر".‬
Sorry, Peter. I have a club meeting today.
‫"(نينا فورتنر)"‬
-What? -Bye.
‫- ماذا؟‬ ‫- إلى اللقاء.‬
She turned you down again, huh?
‫لقد رفضت دعوتك مجددًا، صحيح؟‬
How many times is that now?
‫إذًا كم مرة حتى الآن؟‬
Shut up!
‫اصمت!‬
I'd like to see if anyone can get Nina to agree to a date.
‫أودّ أن أرى من يستطيع إقناع "نينا"‬ ‫بالخروج في موعد غرامي.‬
Uh! I give up!
‫إنني أستسلم!‬
Oh, no! If I'm late with the deliveries, the manager will get mad at me again!
‫بئسًا! إن تأخرت في التسليم،‬ ‫فسيغضب المدير مني مجددًا!‬
I'm home. I'm hungry!
‫لقد عدت إلى المنزل. إنني جائعة!‬
Goodness. The neighbor can probably hear you!
‫يا إلهي. على الأرجح يستطيع أن يسمعك جارنا!‬
It's unbecoming for your age. Wash your hands, okay?
‫هذا لا يليق بعمرك. اغسلي يديك، اتفقنا؟‬
Okay! Hmm?
‫حسنًا! ماذا؟‬
Mom, did you color your hair?
‫أمي، هل صبغت شعرك؟‬
Doesn't it look good?
‫هل يبدو جميلًا؟‬
I can't believe she dyed her hair so bright at her age.
‫لا أصدّق أنها صبغت شعرها‬ ‫بهذا اللون الفاقع في سنّها.‬
Dad, don't say that. She looks lovely!
‫أبي، لا تقل ذلك. إنها تبدو جميلة!‬
It's not like she's going on a parade or something.
‫لن تشارك في مسيرة احتفالية أو ما شابه.‬
Isn't it great that mom can always stay young?
‫أليس من الرائع أن تبقى أمي شابّة دائمًا؟‬
Dad, I'm home.
‫أبي، لقد عدت إلى المنزل.‬
Oh, speaking of parades…
‫بالحديث عن المسيرات الاحتفالية…‬
I saw the kids in their costumes today.
‫رأيت الأطفال في أزياءهم التنكرية اليوم.‬
Ah, the costume parade for St. Adrian Festival.
‫مسيرة الأزياء التنكرية‬ ‫لمهرجان "سانت أدريان".‬
I wish I had dressed up in those costumes when I was little.
‫أتمنى لو كنت قد ارتديت‬ ‫تلك الأزياء التنكرية في طفولتي.‬
They were so cute.
‫كانوا ظرفاء جدًا.‬
You did dress up.
‫كنت ترتدين أزياء تنكرية فعلًا.‬
Isn't that right?
‫أليس كذلك؟‬
Oh, yeah. You did.
‫بلى. كانت ترتديها.‬
Really?
‫حقًا؟‬
Let's see… Here…
‫لنر. هنا…‬
Oh, there it is. It's this one!
‫ها هو. إنه هذا الزيّ!‬
It's true.
‫هذا صحيح.‬
You were so happy and you had so much fun.
‫كنت سعيدة جدًا واستمتعت بوقتك كثيرًا.‬
Do you remember?
‫هل تتذكّر؟‬
Hmm? Yes, you did.
‫ماذا؟ أجل، بالفعل.‬
Costume parade…?
‫مسيرة أزياء تنكرية…؟‬
"A distant spring."
‫"ربيع بعيد."‬
"I forlornly wait for a spring that will never come… Hannah."
‫"أنتظر بفارغ الصبر‬ ‫ربيعًا لن يأتي أبدًا. (هانا)."‬
Oh, Hannah. Can you get over your broken heart already?
‫"هانا". ألن تتجاوزي يومًا‬ ‫مرحلة القلب الجريح؟‬
"Allow me to send you the world's most beautiful flowers."
‫"اسمحي لي بأن أرسل إليك‬ ‫أجمل الزهور في العالم."‬
"I was born to blanket you in flowers."
‫"لقد وُلدت لأدثّرك بالزهور."‬
Wow. I wonder who sent me this.
‫عجبًا. أتساءل من بعث إليّ بهذه الرسالة.‬
I see! Good for you, Peter.
‫فهمت! أحسنت يا "بيتر".‬
How have you been, Nina?
‫كيف حالك يا "نينا"؟‬
I've been feeling well, Dr. Geitel.
‫أنا بخير يا دكتور "غايتل".‬
I'm glad to hear that.
‫يسعدني سماع ذلك.‬
I could tell from the look on your face when you came in
‫تبيّنت من تعبير وجهك حين دخلت‬
the counseling room that you were doing well.
‫إلى غرفة العلاج أنك على ما يُرام.‬
Have you stopped having that dream?
‫هل توقفت عن رؤية ذلك الحلم؟‬
The dream with a monster from the darkness.
‫حلم الوحش الآتي من الظلام.‬
Yes.
‫أجل.‬
I've been sleeping so soundly that I haven't been dreaming at all.
‫صرت أنام بعمق‬ ‫إلى حدّ أنني لا أحلم على الإطلاق.‬
I don't know why I was so plagued by such a dream night after night.
‫لا أعرف لماذا ابتُليت بحلم كهذا‬ ‫الليلة تلو الأخرى.‬
It's common for people to feel insecure when they're students.
‫من الشائع أن يشعر الناس بعدم الأمان‬ ‫في مرحلة الدراسة.‬
Dreams of the future get confused with other worries,
‫تختلط أحلام المستقبل بالهموم الأخرى،‬
so you start to feel lost about who you really are.
‫فتبدئين بالشعور بالضياع‬ ‫حيال هويتك الحقيقية.‬
However, even after living a whole life, it's hard to tell who you really are.
‫ومع ذلك، حتى بعدما تعيشين حياتك بأكملها،‬ ‫من الصعب أن تعرفي من أنت حقًا.‬
All you can do is spend your life wanting to know,
‫كل ما يمكنك فعله هو قضاء حياتك‬ ‫وأنت ترغبين في معرفة ذلك،‬
and just focus on what you can do now for your future.
‫وتركّزين فقط على ما يمكنك فعله الآن‬ ‫من أجل مستقبلك.‬
Yes, I will! I hope to become a public prosecutor.
‫أجل، سأفعل! أتمنى أن أصبح وكيلة نيابة.‬
That's great.
‫هذا رائع.‬
Alright. That's it for today's session.
‫حسنًا. بهذا تنتهي جلسة اليوم.‬
Thank you.
‫شكرًا.‬
Goodbye.
‫إلى اللقاء.‬
Nina Fortner is such a cheerful girl.
‫"نينا فورتنر" فتاة مبتهجة.‬
However, I can't help but feel that
‫لكن، لا يسعني إلا أن أشعر‬
her cheerfulness is a reaction to something she's running away from.
‫بأن ابتهاجها هو ردّ فعل لشيء تهرب منه.‬
Some kind of immense darkness…
‫ظلمة هائلة من نوع ما…‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
Don't pretend you didn't know, Peter.
‫لا تتظاهر بأنك لا تعرف يا "بيتر".‬
I don't understand.
‫لا أفهم.‬
"I was born to blanket you in flowers."
‫"لقد وُلدت لأدثّرك بالزهور."‬
I never thought you had such excellent literary skills.
‫لم أتصوّر أن تكون مهاراتك الأدبية‬ ‫ممتازة إلى هذا الحدّ.‬
I don't know anything about that.
‫لا أعرف شيئًا عن ذلك.‬
Even if you turned me upside down, words like those would never fall out.
‫حتى لو قلبتني رأسًا على عقب،‬ ‫لن تتساقط مني كلمات كهذه أبدًا.‬
Then, who is it?
‫من كتبها إذًا؟‬
I only gave my email address to my friends.
‫لم أعط عنوان بريدي الإلكتروني‬ ‫إلا لأصدقائي.‬
I don't know.
‫لا أعرف.‬
Damn!
‫تبًا!‬
All I know is I have yet another romantic rival.
‫كل ما أعرفه هو أن لي منافسًا رومانسيًا.‬
I wonder who it is.
‫أتساءل من يكون.‬
In this brutal murder case in Munich,
‫في جريمة القتل الوحشية هذه في "ميونيخ"،‬
the perpetrator first killed the parents with a gun.
‫قتل الجاني الوالدين أولًا بمسدس.‬
Then, he strangled the two children with a rope.
‫ثم خنق الطفلين بحبل.‬
From the court records,
‫من سجلّات المحكمة،‬
can anyone explain the judge's ruling?
‫هل يستطيع أحد أن يشرح حكم القاضي؟‬
Miss Nina Fortner?
‫آنسة "نينا فورتنر"؟‬
Did you not understand the question?
‫ألم تفهمي السؤال؟‬
No… Uh… The trial was focused on
‫لا. لقد كان تركيز المحاكمة‬
the cold-blooded murder of the whole family…
‫منصبًا على قتل كل أفراد الأسرة بدم بارد…‬
-Huh? -The evidence…
‫- ماذا؟‬ ‫- الأدلة…‬
The evidence…
‫الأدلة…‬
Huh. There are times you can't answer either, Nina?
‫عجبًا. أنت أيضًا لا يمكنك الإجابة أحيانًا‬ ‫يا "نينا"؟‬
Nina?
‫"نينا"؟‬
What's wrong, Nina?
‫ما الخطب يا "نينا"؟‬
Nina!
‫"نينا"!‬
Are you alright? Do you want to go to the infirmary?
‫هل أنت بخير؟ هل تريدين الذهاب إلى العيادة؟‬
I… I'm fine. I just felt a little faint.
‫لا، أنا بخير. شعرت بشيء من الإعياء فحسب.‬
After listening to the professor…
‫بعد الاستماع إلى الأستاذ…‬
What? About the brutal massacre of the family?
‫ماذا؟ بشأن المذبحة الوحشية لتلك الأسرة؟‬
Stop it!
‫توقف!‬
I thought you were quite a tough person,
‫ظننت أنك شخص قوي جدًا،‬
but you're a lot more sensitive than I expected.
‫لكنك أكثر حساسية مما توقعت.‬
Did you watch terrifying horror films when you were little?
‫هل كنت تشاهدين أفلام رعب مروّعة في طفولتك؟‬
That's it.
‫هذا هو السبب.‬
The counselor, Dr. Geitel, would say this.
‫هكذا كان سيقول المعالج النفسي د. "غايتل".‬
"If you trace it back, it'll be simple."
‫"إن تتبّعت الماضي، فستجدين الأمر بسيطًا.‬
"Let's try to remember some of your childhood."
‫لنحاول تذكّر بعض أحداث طفولتك."‬
-I… -Hmm?
‫أنا…‬
I don't have any memories.
‫ليس لديّ أي ذكريات.‬
I don't remember anything before the age of ten.
‫لا أتذكّر أي شيء قبل سنّ العاشرة.‬
My memories…
‫ذكرياتي…‬
My childhood memories…
‫ذكريات طفولتي…‬
COLOGNE (GERMANY)
‫"(كولونيا)، (ألمانيا)"‬
Both of them were very nice people.
‫كلاهما كانا شخصين لطيفين جدًا.‬
I can't believe the way they were killed.
‫لا أصدّق الطريقة التي قُتلا بها.‬
The children?
‫الولدان؟‬
Yes, I think there was a boy.
‫أجل، أظن أنه كان هناك صبي.‬
I believe his name was Michael. They lived together for two years.
‫أظن أنه كان يُدعى "مايكل".‬ ‫عاشا معًا لمدة عامين.‬
A boy? Was there a boy?
‫صبي؟ هل كان هناك صبي؟‬
Yes, called Michael, I think. He was about 14 years old.
‫أجل، كان يُدعى "مايكل" على ما أظن.‬ ‫كان عمره حوالي 14 عامًا.‬
Oh, Michael? I guess there was someone like that.
‫"مايكل"؟ أظن أنه كان هناك شخص بهذا الاسم.‬
Why are you asking? Are you the police?
‫لماذا تسأل؟ هل أنت من الشرطة؟‬
Yes, Michael Reichmann.
‫أجل، "مايكل رايخمان".‬
He was in my class.
‫كان من تلاميذ صفّي.‬
However, he didn't have much of a presence.
‫ومع ذلك، لم يكن له حضور قوي.‬
I'm a little embarrassed, but I don't remember much about him.
‫أنا محرجة قليلًا،‬ ‫لكنني لا أتذكّر الكثير عنه.‬
I don't even know if he had any friends.
‫لا أعرف حتى لو أنه كان لديه أصدقاء.‬
In addition, there was no record about him, either.
‫بالإضافة إلى ذلك، لم يكن له سجلّ كذلك.‬
There was a fire six years ago, and it burnt everything.
‫نشب حريق قبل ستة أعوام واحترق كل شيء.‬
Six years ago in Cologne,
‫قبل ستة أعوام في "كولونيا"،‬
a young man called Michael was here.
‫كان هناك شابّ يُدعى "مايكل".‬
And Michael's real name is…
‫واسم "مايكل" الحقيقي هو…‬
"Johan"… I guess I used to have that name.
‫"يوهان". يبدو أنه كان اسمي.‬
Who are you?
‫من أنت؟‬
But what's the use of knowing that?
‫لكن ما فائدة معرفة ذلك؟‬
I only know he's a twin and has committed many murders.
‫أعرف فقط أنه أحد توأمين‬ ‫وأنه ارتكب العديد من جرائم القتل.‬
That's all.
‫هذا كل شيء.‬
What am I doing…?
‫ما الذي أفعله؟‬
Twin… What about the sister? Where is his sister?
‫توأم؟ ماذا عن أخته؟ أين أخته؟‬
"I will come for you soon."
‫"سآتي لآخذك قريبًا."‬
Who is this?
‫من هذا؟‬
Saying that he will come for me soon…
‫يقول إنه سيأتي ليأخذني قريبًا…‬
What does it mean?
‫ما معنى ذلك؟‬
A child? Yes, I think it was seven or eight years ago.
‫طفل؟ أظن أن ذلك‬ ‫كان قبل سبعة أو ثمانية أعوام.‬
So Mr. and Mrs. Heinau, who were killed, were fostering a boy?
‫إذًا السيد والسيدة "هايناو" اللذان قُتلا،‬ ‫كانا يرعيان طفلًا؟‬
What was he like?
‫ماذا كانت أوصافه؟‬
"What was he like"?
‫"أوصافه"؟‬
It was such a long time ago.
‫كان هذا قبل زمن طويل جدًّا.‬
And he only lived with them for about a year.
‫وقد عاش معهما تقريبًا لمدة عام واحد فقط.‬
I don't remember anything.
‫لا أتذكّر شيئًا.‬
Did he have a younger sister with him?
‫هل كانت معه أخت صغرى؟‬
It was only a boy.
‫كان صبيًا فحسب.‬
Anyway, I want to forget about what happened to the couple.
‫على أي حال، أريد أن أنسى ما حدث للزوجين.‬
I even thought about moving away after what happened.
‫حتى أنني فكّرت في الانتقال من هنا‬ ‫بعد ما حدث.‬
I know about that boy.
‫أعرف بشأن ذلك الصبي.‬
Come on up. I was about to have some tea.
‫تفضّل بالصعود. كنت على وشك تناول الشاي.‬
Please have a seat.
‫تفضّل بالجلوس.‬
Thank you. Excuse me.
‫شكرًا. معذرةً.‬
Uh, I am--
‫أنا…‬
Sit down.
‫اجلس.‬
Have some tea.
‫تناول بعض الشاي.‬
Uh… Thank you.
‫شكرًا.‬
You're a doctor, right?
‫أنت طبيب، أليس كذلك؟‬
The boy told me about you.
‫حدّثني عنك الصبي.‬
You're Dr. Tenma, aren't you?
‫أنت الدكتور "تينما"، أليس كذلك؟‬
He's coming for you?
‫إنه آت ليأخذك؟‬
Who?
‫من؟‬
I have no idea.
‫لا أعرف.‬
The email was anonymous.
‫كانت الرسالة الإلكترونية من مجهول.‬
You look so happy.
‫تبدو عليك السعادة الشديدة.‬
You can't be thinking a Prince Charming on a white horse
‫لا يمكن أن تتصوّري‬ ‫أن أميرًا ساحرًا على حصان أبيض‬
will be coming for you?
‫آت ليأخذك، صحيح؟‬
Are you jealous?
‫هل تشعرين بالغيرة؟‬
You're daydreaming again, Nina.
‫تراودك أحلام اليقظة من جديد يا "نينا".‬
"I was born to blanket you in flowers."
‫"لقد وُلدت لأدثّرك بالزهور."‬
There aren't any guys who talk like that these days.
‫لا يوجد شبّان‬ ‫يتحدّثون بهذه الطريقة هذه الأيام.‬
Hey! Have you noticed a strange guy in our class recently?
‫اسمعا! هل لاحظتما شابًا غريبًا‬ ‫في صفّنا مؤخرًا؟‬
Oh, yes!
‫أجل!‬
That famous seat in Room 12, where you're bound to be called on.
‫ذلك المقعد الشهير في قاعة المحاضرات 12،‬ ‫حيث لا يمكن تفادي نداء الأساتذة.‬
The guy just sat there calmly,
‫جلس الشابّ هناك في هدوء،‬
but he never got called on by the professor.
‫لكن الأستاذ لم يناده.‬
Yes! And did you know?
‫أجل! وهل أخبركما بشيء آخر؟‬
During the class, he kept staring at Nina.
‫في أثناء المحاضرة، ظلّ يحدّق في "نينا".‬
-Huh? -That's him!
‫- ماذا؟‬ ‫- هذا هو!‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
What else?
‫وماذا غير ذلك؟‬
The Prince Charming!
‫الأمير الساحر!‬
That boy was highly grateful to you.
‫كان ذلك الفتى ممتنًا جدًا لك.‬
Dr. Tenma.
‫يا دكتور "تينما".‬
He said that you saved his life and you meant more to him than his parents.
‫قال إنك أنقذت حياته‬ ‫وإنك أعزّ إليه من والديه.‬
What name did he call himself?
‫بم كان يسمّي نفسه؟‬
Franz…
‫"فرانز"…‬
But he said it wasn't his real name.
‫لكنه قال إنه ليس اسمه الحقيقي.‬
so he trusted you that much?
‫أي أنه كان يثق بك إلى هذا الحدّ؟‬
Franz, who showed out of nowhere,
‫"فرانز"، الذي ظهر من حيث لا ندري،‬
was taken in by Mr. and Mrs. Heinau who lived in the flat across the hall.
‫آواه الزوجان "هايناو"‬ ‫اللذان كانا يقيمان في الشقة المقابلة.‬
He was with them for a year.
‫مكث معهما عامًا واحدًا.‬
No, actually. It was 14 months
‫لا، بل مكث معهما 14 شهرًا،‬
from March 1987 to April 1988.
‫من مارس 1987 إلى أبريل 1988.‬
Then one day, he just disappeared.
‫وذات يوم، اختفى فجأة.‬
He was very bright and well-mannered.
‫كان ذكيًا ومهذبًا جدًا.‬
Did he come to this room?
‫هل كان يأتي إلى هذه الغرفة؟‬
Every day.
‫كل يوم.‬
I live alone, so I always welcomed him here.
‫إنني أعيش وحدي، لذا كنت أرحّب به دائمًا.‬
He would sit in that chair and study diligently.
‫كان يجلس على ذلك الكرسي ويدرس بجدّ.‬
I taught him English and French, and he mastered them in a flash.
‫علّمته الإنجليزية والفرنسية،‬ ‫وأجادهما في لمح البصر.‬
Before he disappeared, he was fluent in both languages.
‫قبل اختفائه، كان يتكلّم اللغتين بطلاقة.‬
He was only 12 years old.
‫لم يكن قد تجاوز الـ12 من العمر.‬
Can you recall anything else about him?
‫هل تتذكّر أي شيء آخر عنه؟‬
He listened to my stories attentively.
‫كان ينصت إلى قصصي بانتباه.‬
What stories do you think he was most interested in?
‫ما أكثر القصص‬ ‫التي كانت تثير اهتمامه في تصوّرك؟‬
The war stories.
‫قصص الحرب.‬
The war?
‫الحرب؟‬
During World War II,
‫في أثناء الحرب العالمية الثانية،‬
I was on the crew of a U-boat.
‫كنت ضمن طاقم غواصة حربية ألمانية.‬
His favorite story was
‫كانت قصته المفضّلة‬
about the time we were attacked by one of the Allies' destroyers.
‫هي قصة تعرّضنا إلى الهجوم‬ ‫من إحدى مدمّرات الحلفاء.‬
We were attacked by the enemy at a depth of 120 meters,
‫هاجمنا العدوّ على عمق 120 مترًا،‬
but we kept going even after we suffered a fatal blow.
‫لكننا واصلنا التقدّم‬ ‫حتى بعد تعرّضنا إلى ضربة قاتلة.‬
The vessel was creaking under the pressure, and we all waited in terror.
‫كانت الغوّصة تتصدّع تحت الضغط،‬ ‫وانتظرنا جميعًا في رعب.‬
We returned from that living hell 38 hours later.
‫عدنا من ذلك الجحيم بعد 38 ساعة.‬
Ordinary children would listen to it as a story of adventure.
‫أي طفل عادي سيستمع إليها باعتبارها مغامرة.‬
But he was different.
‫لكن هذا الصبي كان مختلفًا.‬
He was mostly interested in…
‫كان ما يهمه في الغالب…‬
the terror.
‫هو الرعب.‬
The extreme terror.
‫الرعب الشديد.‬
What is the reaction of a person standing on the edge of death?
‫ما هو ردّ فعل شخص يقف على حافة الموت؟‬
That boy was only interested in that.
‫كان الصبي مهتمًا بذلك فحسب.‬
He took pleasure in terror.
‫كان يستمتع بالرعب.‬
Wh… What kind of expression did he have while he was listening to your stories?
‫ما التعبير الذي علا وجهه‬ ‫بينما كان يستمع إلى قصصك؟‬
Probably with a gleam in his eyes, and a smile on his face.
‫على الأرجح‬ ‫كان في عينيه بريق وعلى وجهه ابتسامة.‬
Probably?
‫على الأرجح؟‬
You see, I'm blind.
‫أنا أعمى.‬
Yes. I don't know that boy's real name,
‫أجل. لا أعرف الاسم الحقيقي لذلك الصبي،‬
and I don't even know what he looked like.
‫ولا أعرف حتى ما كانت أوصافه.‬
Earlier, you said that he trusted me.
‫قبل قليل، أنت قلت إنه كان يثق بي.‬
In fact, he doesn't trust anyone.
‫في الواقع، إنه لا يثق بأحد.‬
There is only one person he trusts.
‫إنه لا يثق إلا بشخص واحد فقط.‬
It was his sister.
‫أخته.‬
He said he would go to collect her when she was 20 years old.
‫قال إنه سيذهب لإحضارها‬ ‫حين يصبح عمرها 20 عامًا.‬
Go where?
‫إلى أين سيذهب؟‬
To Heidelberg.
‫إلى "هايدلبرغ".‬
I'm heading out!
‫سأخرج!‬
Ride your scooter safely!
‫اركبي دراجتك بأمان!‬
Okay!
‫حسنًا!‬
Bye, Dad!
‫إلى اللقاء يا أبي!‬
Be careful.
‫اعتني بنفسك.‬
Bye!
‫إلى اللقاء!‬
It's… time.
‫لقد حان الوقت.‬
But…
‫لكن…‬
Didn't we decide already?
‫ألم نقرر بالفعل؟‬
We would tell her on her 20th birthday…
‫اتفقنا على أن نخبرها في عيد ميلادها الـ20…‬
that she's not our child.
‫بأنها ليست ابنتنا.‬
Wait. I can't.
‫مهلًا. لا أستطيع.‬
What are you talking about? Didn't you want to meet him?
‫عمّ تتحدّثين؟ ألم ترغبي في مقابلته؟‬
We told him to come here
‫طلبنا منه أن يأتي إلى هنا‬
and meet you here.
‫ويلتقي بك هنا.‬
Good luck with your Prince Charming.
‫حظًا موفقًا مع أميرك الساحر.‬
See you later!
‫سنراك لاحقًا!‬
Hey, Clara! Beate!
‫"كلارا"! "بيتي"!‬
I can't believe they did this.
‫لا أصدّق أنهما قد فعلتا ذلك.‬
-Hey, look! -He's coming!
‫- انظري!‬ ‫- إنه قادم!‬
Hel… Hello. Are you Ms. Nina Fortner?
‫مرحبًا. هل أنت الآنسة "نينا فورتنر"؟‬
Ye… Yes.
‫أجل.‬
Um… My name is Otto Hubermann.
‫اسمي "أوتو هوبرمان".‬
Oh… Hello.
‫مرحبًا.‬
Who…
‫من…‬
Who is that?
‫من هذا؟‬
I've seen him… somewhere… before.
‫رأيته في مكان ما من قبل.‬
Who… are you?
‫من أنت؟‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
-Nina!
‫- "نينا"!‬
-What happened?
‫- ماذا حدث؟‬
What's wrong? Are you okay?
‫ما الخطب؟ هل أنت بخير؟‬
Nina! Wake up!
‫"نينا"! أفيقي!‬
-Nina! -Are you alright?
‫- "نينا"!‬ ‫- هل أنت على ما يُرام؟‬
Subtitle translation by: Sandy Huang
‫ترجمة "مي بدر"‬